mercedesclub.org.uk 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Mercedes Benz Owners

###  Privacy Policy

The Mercedes-Benz Owners do not disclose buyers information to third parties. 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We also use this information along with IP addresses & browser details to improve our products and services. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our websites.

Although we take the privacy and security of your details very seriously, use of the Web Site by you is subject to the risk that unauthorised third parties may access or intercept your personal information. We assume no responsibility for the acts of any such unauthorised third parties. Because of the nature of the internet, your personal information may be transmitted across routes which take it outside the European Union. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

If you have any queries in relation to use of your personal information, please contact our customer services department: correspondence address - Mercedes-Benz Owners, Langton Road, Langton Green, Tunbridge Wells, Kent, TN3 0EG; telephone - 01892 860922; e-mail address - info@mercedesclub.org.uk
